Now, module seven, emotional resilience.
This is where a lot of my words come through in this, in this, this lesson, you know, the
other modules, of course, in my words come through.
But this one is where I really resonate with you guys, you first gen students, you know,
the course objectives to find imposter syndrome, imposter syndrome is very real, especially
as a first generation student, you feel like, you know, there are plenty of times where
I went to UNC, I went to class, I hear everything about what every other student was doing, and
I felt like I truly did not belong here, like I was not meant to be at the school because
everybody's just so, you know, in tune, they're so ready.
But imposter syndrome is real, and I don't want you to think that it's not because you
truly do belong here, you are at the school for a reason.
Never doubt that you're too, I don't know, stupid or idiotic to have even gone to the
school, everybody is on their own way.
So just keep that out there, you are, you are here because you meant to be here.
Code switching, I'll also be going into that, but code switching is important.
It's not really important, but code switching, you know, it's a tactic, it happens, you know,
when you're, when you're talking to a group of people that you don't really, you know,
you're not familiar with, you can't talk the same way you did at home.
But what's important is that you find the resources you find, you know, being in a club,
extracurricular sports, where you don't need to do that, you know, as a Southeast Asian
myself, I was gravitating towards the Southeast Asian Student Association, my freshman year,
and I really felt like I belonged there, and it was great.
I didn't need to code switch, I didn't need to feel the imposter syndrome, finding a place
where you belong, where you truly feel like you belong, is, is a blessing in disguise that
you may not have, you know, ever needed, because if I wasn't in that association, I wouldn't
have, I wouldn't have really, you know, felt like I belonged at UNC, identified at least
two campus mental health resources that can be at UNC, it's CAHPS career, and you know,
it's counseling and something like that, your counseling center, apply at least one concrete
coping strategy for modules.
My coping strategy, whenever I get stretched out or overwhelmed, I just take a little break
and maybe I'll cook, you know, do something that you enjoy, maybe I'll do a little gaming,
maybe I'll, I'll watch some YouTube or watch an anime, like really just make sure you're
coping is, you know, it doesn't have to be productive, but make sure it's not, you know,
unhealthy for you, make sure it's something that you enjoy doing, and it actually takes
your mind off of things.
Right, honestly, about both the fear and the strength you're bringing to your first college
semester, when I was there, when I was at UNC, my first college semester, I didn't do
that, but a fear and a strength that I had, a fear that I had, it's going to be hard to
be rigorous. I like, I don't feel ready. I don't think I am ready. I don't know anything
about college, but a strength that I had was I was just passionate about learning. I wanted
to make sure that, you know, I made college my own, my own experience. Yeah, it's really
hard to make sure that you are taking the time to take care of yourself, you know, as a first
gen student, you may not know how to navigate through college, but you're not alone. There
are plenty of other first generation college students. I mean, I, at UNC, I was a, was a
Carolina Covenant, and a lot of Carolina Covenants are first generation college students.
There are first gen organizations, so make sure you find the people that you truly resonate
with. You are not alone. But if you are in a crisis, I included everything that, all
the contact information that you may need. So you got this, conscious syndrome is real.
Don't act like you're the only person that has it. Code switching is real. Find your
people and make sure that you take care of yourself. That should end up module seven.
So other than that, great job at getting to this point.